In this module, you learned a little bit about deployment, and in particular,
在此模块中 你学习了部署知识
you learned how you can use SageMaker to
你学习了如何使用 SageMaker
create and deploy your own machine learning projects.
创建和部署你自己的机器学习项目
Before you go, let's talk a little bit about the different things that we learned about,
在继续学习之前 先回顾下我们所学的各个知识点
starting with the notebook instances.
从 notebook 实例开始
For the most part, we've been using
在大部分情况下
the notebook instance as our primary touchpoint for SageMaker,
我们一直都使用 notebook 实例与 SageMaker 交互
and it will likely be the case that this is
并且你以后很可能
your main method of interacting with SageMaker as well.
也主要通过这种方式与 SageMaker 交互
It provides a convenient place to do some data processing,
你可以在 notebook 实例中处理数据
and then ask SageMaker to perform various computations to help you train and test models.
然后要求 SageMaker 执行各种计算 帮助你训练和测试模型
We also talked about training jobs,
我们还讨论了训练作业
we perform training jobs using the high-level approach
我们使用高阶方法执行了训练作业
by letting SageMaker take care of setting up the job specifics.
让 SageMaker 设定训练作业的参数
Later on, we looked at how we can define those job specifics ourselves.
之后 我们学习了如何自己定义这些作业参数
Then, when we wanted to train a bunch of training jobs to test various hyperparameters,
然后 我们训练了多个训练作业来测试各种超参数
we learned that we could use SageMaker's hyperparameter tuning jobs to do that.
我们可以使用 SageMaker 的超参数优化作业完成这一步
We also learned how to create models,
我们还学习了如何创建模型
which in SageMaker is a collection of data.
在 SageMaker 中 模型是一个数据集合
Essentially, it is a pairing of
实际上模型就是
model artifacts that were created during a training process,
在训练过程中创建的模型工件
and a container that contains code that uses those model artifacts to perform inference.
与包含代码的容器的组合 这些代码将使用模型工件进行推理
We also talked about endpoint configurations,
我们还讨论了端点配置
these described to SageMaker how a specific endpoint should be set up,
端点配置指定了 SageMaker 应该如何设置某个端点
so that when data is sent to it,
当数据发送给端点时
it gets forwarded on to the correct model.
数据会转发到正确的模型
In some cases, you may even want to have an endpoint send data to multiple models.
在某些情形下 甚至需要端点向多个模型发送数据
In addition, we saw how once we have an endpoint configuration,
此外 我们知道有了端点配置后
we can ask SageMaker to create an endpoint.
可以要求 SageMaker 创建端点
Currently, I don't have any endpoints running because as I've mentioned many times,
目前 我们没有任何在运行的端点 因为我多次提到
you are charged for the length of time that an endpoint is running,
端点按照运行时长计费
so if you don't have no use for it, you should shut it down.
所以不使用的时候 应该关闭端点
A very useful functionality that we also discussed is a batch transform job.
我们还学习了一个很有用的功能 叫做批转换作业
What this allows us to do is to perform inference on a whole bunch of data all at once,
该作业使我们能够同时对大量数据进行推理
and it provides a very convenient way of doing so,
并且流程很方便
so that we don't have to first deploy the model and then send our datapoints bit-by-bit,
我们不需要首先部署模型 然后一点一点地发送数据点
making sure to shut it down at the end.
最后还要关闭端点
SageMaker takes care of all of that for us,
SageMaker 将为我们完成所有这些步骤
launching the instance that performs inference,
包括启动执行推理的实例
sending all the data to that model,
将所有数据发送给该模型
and then shutting down the completed since once it's finished.
然后在运行完毕后关闭计算功能
I personally think that SageMaker is a great tool
我个人认为 SageMaker 是一个很棒的工具
for quickly developing machine learning jobs,
可以帮助我们快速开发机器学习作业
and then being able to start putting those things into production.
然后将这些作业部署到生产环境
I hope that you have a great time using SageMaker in your own projects,
希望你能在你自己的项目中有效地利用 SageMaker
and I look forward to see what you make.
迫不及待地想要看到你的作品了